<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Changes</title>
  </properties>
  <body>
    <release version="2.0.16">

    </release>

    <release version="2.0.15">
      <action dev="fschwarz" type="add">
        Add of property skip in order to skip execution of the plugin.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Add of a new target "generate-titlepage" in order generate titlepage stylesheet that may be needed to configure
        some customization layers. A sample configuration is available on "docbkx.template" profile.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Allow to pass xsl and some docbkx parameters using the command line or pom properties, they are prefixed with
        "docbkx.". Example mvn docbkx:generate-pdf -Ddocbkx.draftMode="true"
      </action>
      <action dev="andreas.veithen" type="update">
        The xxxCustomization parameter is now properly interpreted relative to basedir.
      </action>
      <action dev="frank.schwarz.78" type="add">
        Add of a possibility to skip execution of this plug-in.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        The plugin incorrectly report up-to-date generated PDF when xInclude is used, now when xInclude
        is used files are regenerated because you do not have much handles on the xml processor for now.
      </action>
      <action dev="tdemande" type="update">
        Uppate to latest webhelp-indexer compatible with docbook stylesheets in 1.78.1.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Add of a generate-manpage sample.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        "docbkx.external" sample was using an hardcoded path in externalFOPConfiguration.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        Update to FOP 1.1 to support hyphenateVerbatim option.
      </action>
      <action dev="samharwell" type="update">
        Allow project to specify source file encoding, default UTF-8.
      </action>
      <action dev="vincent.nap" type="add">
        Add of a new target "generate-xhtml5".
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Allow the targets to generate xref database files, they will be named &lt;filename&gt;.&lt;extension&gt;.target.db
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Add of a new target "generate-epub3".
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Update copyright headers and setup maven-license-plugin.
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.14">
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
        Add of property showXslMessages in order to activate the print of xsl:messages, default is set to false.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        The plugin version is not anymore harcoded in the archetype
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        The property base.dir for html output in non chunking mode was not set thus causing long description to be
        generated in the root dir.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        The new docbook stylesheets make use of property epubEmbeddedFonts instead of epubEmbeddedFont previously
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        The webhelp output to correctly set the language
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
        Due to the remove of a maven annotation the external fop configuration was not taken into account anymore
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.13">
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Update of samples to use docbook namespace stylesheets (remove of DTD usage)
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Fo outputs (pdf and rtf) were not correctly defining the output filename when multiple input files were given
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
The jalopy:format plugin has suppressed many maven javadoc tags causing many docbkx plugins to not work as expected
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
The WebHelp indexer is now correctly resetting the indexer
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.12">
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Outputs having the property useStandardOutput set to false will generate their content to a dedicated directory using
the input filename as directory name. Current outputs concerned are: (x)html chunked, epub, webhelp, man, eclipse, javahelp
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Move to FOP 1.0
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Remove deprecated maven configuration keys, mandatory for maven 3 fresh install to compile the plugin
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Move to docbook xsl stylesheets 1.76.1
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
Add support for WebHelp output. WebHelp is a feature-rich, nice looking XSL customization and is a better
alternative for web deployments.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
Add support for RTF output (Rich Text Format)
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
EPUB output was not correctly zipping content when multiple input documents were specified
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.11">
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Docbook XML catalogs of both previous and current versions are now correctly loaded.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
Add of epub plugin
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
docbkx-tools plugin now works correctly under maven 3
      </action>
        <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Bugs in the fop-support plugin was causing the plugin to stop and not working when space characters
were encountered into the path.
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.10">
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
Add of optional &lt;useStandardOutput/&gt; in docbkx-builder-maven-plugin and the generated
Mojos for stylesheets directly writing the target filename (manpages ...)
instead of using stdout as transformation result.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Use of latest docbook stylesheets artifacts as dependency instead of embedding parts
of docbook stylesheet distribution.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
Add of docbkx-quickstart-archetype (@see http://code.google.com/p/docbkx-tools/wiki/UsingArchetypeTemplate)
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
Fails to create directory with xom xinclude
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
Add of XHTML support (generate-xhtml goal)
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.9">
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
	Correction of generation failure when spaces in path.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
	Moved to FOP 0.95.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
	Removed use of ExpressionUtils class to avoid property clashes.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
	Added support of http url in xxxCustomization parameters.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
	Added generate-javahelp goal.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
	Added support for setting additional XSL parameters which are not
	part of the regular docbook parameters using
	&lt;customizationParameters&gt;.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
	Added support for setting system properties using &lt;systemProperties&gt;
	which contains &lt;name&gt; &lt;value&gt; elements pair inside &lt;property&gt; elements.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
	XSLT Highlighting can now be configured with &lt;xslthlConfig&gt; property or
	using &lt;systemProperties&gt;.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="update">
	Enhancement of urn:docbkx:stylesheet which points to the docbook release stylesheet
	to allow urn:docbkx:stylesheet/xxxx to point to other files of the docbook release.
	Example: &lt; import href="urn:docbkx:stylesheet/pagesetup.xsl" /&gt;.
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.8"
	     description="Better PDF support and stylesheet update">
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added support for alternative fonts in PDF output.
      </action>
      <action dev="wis" type="update">
	Replaced FOP 0.20.5 with FOP 0.94.
      </action>
      <action dev="wis" type="update">
	Moved on to version 1.73.2 of the DocBook XSL stylesheets.
      </action>
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Made sure that documents are not re-built when the sources did
	not change.
      </action>
      <action dev="mimil" type="add">
	Better support for XInclude allowing includes by id and xml:id.
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.7"
	     description="Syntax highlighting support"
	     date="5-10-2007">
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added support for syntax highlighting.
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.6"
	     description="Eclipse help support"
	     date="27-7-2007">
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added rudimentary support for generating Eclipse help.
      </action>
    </release>
    
    <release version="2.0.5"
	     description="DocBook stylesheets upgrade + expression language">
      <action dev="wis" type="update">
	Upgraded the styleseets to version 1.72.0.
      </action>
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added experimental support for using expression language in
	processing instructions. 
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.4"
	     description="DocBook stylesheets upgrade">
      <action dev="wis" type="update">
	Upgraded the stylesheets to version 1.70.1.
      </action>
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.3"
	     description="Customization enhancements">

      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added support for inserting customization stylesheets. Simply
	set the foCustomization or htmlCustomization properties, and
	link the original stylesheets back in by using a symbolic
	xsl:import. After that, you can use all Bob Sagehills
	sugestions for customization the output.
      </action>

      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added support for type specific content. The plugin will by
	default look for a file called docbbkx.{type}.ent. If it
	exists, then it will be automatically included in the XML
	document.
      </action>
      
    </release>

    <release version="2.0.2"
	     description="A few enhancements and bug fixes.">
      <action dev="wis" type="fix">
	Fixed support for xinclude.
      </action>
    </release>
    
    <release version="2.0.1" 
	     description="Only version number update."
	     date="2006-10-23">

      <action dev="wis" type="update">
	Updated all version numbers to be in sync. (So the link to the
	specific version of the DocBook templates has been dropped.)
      </action>

    </release>

    <release version="1.69.1.7"
	     description="Support for XInclude">
      
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added support for XInclude. You can now instruct the plugin to
	process xinclude tags by setting the 'xincludeSupport'
	property to true.
      </action>

    </release>

    <release version="1.69.1.6" 
	     description="Handling unparsed entity references.">
      
      <action dev="wis" type="fix">
	Unparsed entity references were not handled correctly. As a
	result, images would not appear in PDF and HTML output.
      </action>

    </release>
    
    <release version="1.69.1.5"
	     description="Chunked output and Java 1.4 compliance.">

      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added support for chunked HTML output.
      </action>

      <action dev="wis" type="update">
	Refactored the code to be Java 1.4 compliant.
      </action>
      
      <action dev="wis" type="add">
	Added a user guide.
      </action>

    </release>

    
  </body>
</document>
